[
  {
    "qID": 1,
    "learningGoal": 1,
    "question": "What is a cat?",
    "choices": ["Dog", "Elephant", "Turtle", "Cat"],
    "answer": "Cat"
  },
  {
    "qID": 2,
    "learningGoal": 1,
    "question": "What is a typical lifespan of a cat?",
    "choices": ["12-18 years", "20-22 years", "0-4 years", "6-12 years"],
    "answer": "12-18 years"
  },
  {
    "qID": 3,
    "learningGoal": 1,
    "question": "Which is NOT a breed of cat?",
    "choices": ["Siamese", "British Shorthair", "Persian", "Poodle"],
    "answer": "Poodle"
  },
  {
    "qID": 4,
    "learningGoal": 1,
    "question": "What do cats love?",
    "choices": ["Watermelon", "Onions", "Catnip", "Dog Food"],
    "answer": "Catnip"
  },
  {
    "qID": 5,
    "learningGoal": 1,
    "question": "What is a baby cat called?",
    "choices": ["Foal", "Kitten", "Puppy", "Hatchling"],
    "answer": "Kitten"
  },

  {
    "qID": 6,
    "learningGoal": 2,
    "question": "Where are the headquarters of Subaru?",
    "choices": ["Japan", "Korea", "China", "Germany"],
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "qID": 7,
    "learningGoal": 2,
    "question": "Which car of the following is not a model of Honda?",
    "choices": ["Accord", "Pilot", "Camry", "Civic"],
    "answer": "Camry"
  },
  {
    "qID": 8,
    "learningGoal": 2,
    "question": "What is the best selling car of all time?",
    "choices": [
      "Toyota Corolla",
      "Ford Model T",
      "Volkswagen Beetle",
      "Subaru Impreza"
    ],
    "answer": "Toyota Corolla"
  },
  {
    "qID": 9,
    "learningGoal": 2,
    "question": "What is a car?",
    "choices": ["Airplane", "Boat", "Car", "Aircraft Carrier"],
    "answer": "Car"
  },
  {
    "qID": 10,
    "learningGoal": 2,
    "question": "How many people can you safely fit into a Honda Accord?",
    "choices": ["5", "4", "7", "13"],
    "answer": "5"
  },

  {
    "qID": 11,
    "learningGoal": 3,
    "question": "What is NOT a berry?",
    "choices": ["Blueberry", "Strawberry", "Raspberry", "Banana"],
    "answer": "Strawberry"
  },
  {
    "qID": 12,
    "learningGoal": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is considered a tropical fruit",
    "choices": ["Apple", "Grape", "Papaya", "Orange"],
    "answer": "Papaya"
  },
  {
    "qID": 13,
    "learningGoal": 3,
    "question": "What was the first vegetable grown in space?",
    "choices": ["Celery", "Potato", "Squash", "Carrot"],
    "answer": "Potato"
  },
  {
    "qID": 14,
    "learningGoal": 3,
    "question": "What apple variant is native to North America?",
    "choices": ["Crabapple", "Gala", "Honeycrisp", "Empire"],
    "answer": "Crabapple"
  },
  {
    "qID": 15,
    "learningGoal": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a citrus fruit",
    "choices": ["Orange", "Pomelo", "Lime", "Watermelon"],
    "answer": "Watermelon"
  },

  {
    "qID": 16,
    "learningGoal": 4,
    "question": "Which is not a starter pokemon in Pokemon Emerald?",
    "choices": ["Mudkip", "Treeko", "Torchic", "Squirtle"],
    "answer": "Squirtle"
  },
  {
    "qID": 17,
    "learningGoal": 4,
    "question": "what is the bestselling Pokemon game?",
    "choices": [
      "Pokemon Red/Green/Blue",
      "Pokemon Leafgreen/Firered",
      "Pokemon Heartgold/Soulsilver",
      "Pokemon Pearl/Diamond"
    ],
    "answer": "Pokemon Red/Green/Blue"
  },
  {
    "qID": 18,
    "learningGoal": 4,
    "question": "Which pokemon is the only pokemon that can devolve?",
    "choices": ["Raichu", "Slowbro", "Machamp", "Torterra"],
    "answer": "Slowbro"
  },
  {
    "qID": 19,
    "learningGoal": 4,
    "question": "What was the first pokemon ever created?",
    "choices": ["Pikachu", "Rayquaza", "Rhydon", "Pidgey"],
    "answer": "Rhydon"
  },
  {
    "qID": 20,
    "learningGoal": 4,
    "question": "what type of Pokemon are effective against Normal type Pokemon?",
    "choices": ["Fighting", "Dragon", "Ice", "Bug"],
    "answer": "Fighting"
  }
]
